[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 43, "question": "How will that play for the prosecution given that she's such a crucial witness?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 44, "answer": "Right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "EX", "."], "qSentId": 66, "question": "What do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 67, "answer": "Well, you know, she was an unusually difficult witness to evaluate because she was like a surly kid up there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "CC", "VBZ", "RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 83, "question": "And Jayne Weintraub, I mean, if you take that at face value and that is the truth, that's a pretty devastating indictment of what George Zimmerman did, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 84, "answer": "Well, it is and isn't, Piers, because you have to remember the only issue here really is self- defense.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jayne Weintraub", "George Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Do you watch \"First 48\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "``", "NNP", "CD", "''", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "I didn't hear you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "``", "NNP", "CD", ",", "''", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "IN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "I'm sorry, the \"First 48\"?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "DT", "``", "NNP", "CD", "''", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "A show, the \"First 48,\" when a victim died, they call the number that the victim called before, and they have it.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "IN", "VBN", "TO", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 118, "question": "Is that significant?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 119, "answer": "Well, I think it is interesting that young people often learn about the criminal justice system from television, as opposed to in school.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 146, "question": "What's that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 147, "answer": "I'm leaving today.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 151, "question": "How much more time do you think that you need to finish your cross?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "RBR", "NN", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 152, "answer": "I certainly wouldn't -- I don't know for sure.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 160, "question": "You know, it's not a pleasant experience, is it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 161, "answer": "No, and I have to say, you know, the candor and the honesty, I mean, I just love that moment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 188, "question": "Or are they arresting him because the other guys already flipped and turned against him?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBN", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 189, "answer": "That's the biggest question.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", ":", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "VBN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "Now, Gloria, how significant could that be in all this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "JJ", "MD", "IN", "VB", "IN", "DT", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "Well, if, in fact, it's the same gun that was used, we don't know because -- and by the way, the search warrants have been sealed, the records have been sealed, so we really don't know.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Gloria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":"], "qSentId": 205, "question": "There is this culture, isn't it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "I think --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 207, "question": "Of NFL players of having a gun, empowering themselves with a weapon?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBG", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 208, "answer": "I think there is a culture of guns among young people, and I think that's the issue.", "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["NFL"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "VB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 243, "question": "Are you frustrated, though, despite the success, that what we didn't get today from the Supreme Court was a decision on a homosexual's constitutional right to get married in America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", ",", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 244, "answer": "Well, what you did get was a decision that I think lays the groundwork for decisions all across the country to establish marriage equality in every one of the 50 states.", "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["today"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Supreme Court"], "LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David"]}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "WP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 252, "question": "What is your reaction to what Cardinal Dolan said?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 253, "answer": "My reaction - my reaction is the same as that, and I want to amplify what David said.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Cardinal Dolan"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 279, "question": "When do you see America, given the way and the speed this is moving, actually moving to what California has in totality?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", ",", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "WP", "NNP", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 280, "answer": "I don't know that -- because it was very difficult to hear your full question.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America", "California"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":"], "qSentId": 333, "question": "A tragedy?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "Well --", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Dolan"]}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "POS", "RB", ",", "RB", "RB", "NNP", ",", "TO", "RB", "VBP", "RP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "POS", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", ",", "IN", "POS", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "CC", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 336, "question": "That's a tragedy for America?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 337, "answer": "I think if you want to reject the right of the Catholic bishop's collectively, not just Dolan, to actually stand up for their values and you want to say that's -- and you want to trivialize it, that's your right, but in fact, I do believe states are making arrangements.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Kim Kardashian"]}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJR", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 347, "question": "Is this a tragedy for America, Van?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 348, "answer": "Well, first of all, I just want to say, as a Christian, if you're concerned about traditional marriage, Kim Kardashian has done more harm to traditional marriage than any gay person.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "``", "NN", "''", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "CD", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 410, "question": "Van, any good?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 411, "answer": "Well, you know, part of the reason we want to have this show \"CROSSFIRE\" is because the show, which we haven't talked about that much, is going to be a half hour long and we're going to have one topic at a time so we can actually get deep into this stuff.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Martin, just procedurally what is likely to happen tomorrow?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "WP", "VBZ", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "Well, I mean, you know, if you were a viewer and if you're a court watcher and you liked this afternoon, you're going to love tomorrow because it's going to be more of the same.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 469, "question": "And on a bigger picture, do you think we're going to see Zimmerman give evidence himself?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "VB", "NN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 470, "answer": "Not a chance.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Zimmerman"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "And in terms of the bigger issues this case raises, race being a factor as many people feared or is it really coming down to a test of Florida's self-defense laws?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJR", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", ",", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "VBN", "CC", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "Well, criminal trials are really always about individual cases.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Florida"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 522, "question": "How do you collectively as a team deal with that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 523, "answer": "Well, I mean we rely on each other a lot.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "How does he deal with the particular pressure that he gets, because it's extraordinary?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "VBZ", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "It is extraordinary.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 547, "question": "Do you think that you're going to see more professional athlete now having the courage perhaps spurred on by American public -- to be more open about things like their sexuality?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "JJ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", ":", "TO", "VB", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 548, "answer": "I think so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "Am I not trying hard enough?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "Yes, I'm just a lucky guy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 573, "question": "Against us?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 574, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 578, "question": "To be a champion?", "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 579, "answer": "Oh, boy.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 588, "question": "Just generally, how do you deal with that kind of game where you just about get away with it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 589, "answer": "Well, you just have to play the game and luckily it went our way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 604, "question": "Will LeBron be with you next year?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 605, "answer": "Thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130626pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 608, "question": "All right?", "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 609, "answer": "That's right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]